smartdate.com 2001-12-05

# MARKEM Privacy Policy

| Your privacy, and the privacy of all users of MARKEM.com, is important to us. Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy. Our policy is based on the principles of notice, choice and access in the collection and use of all information regarding our users and their activities at our site. **1\. Notice**

This policy tells you, among other things, the types of information we gather from you, how we may use or disclose that information and our efforts to protect it. Please read this policy carefully, and feel free to contact us at [webmaster@markem.com](mailto:webmaster@markem.com) if you have any questions regarding its contents.

In connection with your use of our site, we ask for and may collect a variety of information from and about you in different ways. For example, when you request information from our site, we ask for and store your and/or your business' name, title, address, email address and other identifying contact data. In addition, we collect information about your specific requests, comments and suggestions. We may also collect the information you disclose in any of our chat rooms, discussion groups and bulletin boards, when they become available.  
Use of our site might require that you accept the use of cookies, which are small data files that our Web site might send to your browser for storage on your computer's hard drive. We may use cookies to protect confidential data, track activity at our site and better serve your needs and interests.  
We use your personally identifying information to identify you as a user of the site and to respond to your inquiries, identify market trends and formulate business plans. If you grant us permission to contact you about our products and services, we may use your email address to contact you directly regarding services or products that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also associate your personally identifying information with information we collect about your preferences and activities at the site, such as the particular pages you request at the site and purchases or other transactions you effect through or based on information on the site. We may vary the content you receive in future visits to the site based on your preferences and activities.

We may combine your personally identifying information, and information about your preferences and activities, with those of all or a particular group of our users to prepare collective profiles of our users and their activities. For example, we may track the number of our users who view certain pages or use certain features or compile the total dollar amount of sales conducted through or based on our site in a particular geographic region. Such information, and other information we derive from individual users' information, allows us to continue to grow and provide you with quality fellow users through more accurate marketing and advertising of our Web site.  

If you grant us permission to provide your personally identifying information and information about your activities and preferences to other companies wishing to contact you about products or services, we may provide such information to such other companies, but we will only provide the information to those companies that we believe impose reasonable safeguards on the privacy of your information. We may also provide third parties with collective profiles of our user groups and their activities and preferences but such collective profiles will not include information identifying you. Such collective profiles may also be disclosed in describing our site and services to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.  

Finally, we may disclose information to fulfill certain legal and regulatory requirements or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others' rights or to prevent harm. 

We will request your permission to send your personally identifying information to others, and if you do not grant such permission we will restrict the use of your information to maintaining your use of the site.  

In addition, we will not send unsolicited messages to users of our site who do not indicate that they wish to receive such messages.

At any time after you have logged on to our site, you may contact us at webmaster@markem.com to request access to information we have collected regarding you or your business or to notify us of changes to such information. If you request any such changes, we will contact you by email or fax to confirm those changes. Once confirmed, any new item of information will replace the corresponding information previously provided.

|   |
